export const dart = [
    {
        question: "What is Dart?",
        option1: "A web browser",
        option2: "A programming language",
        option3: "A database management system",
        option4: "An operating system",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Who developed Dart?",
        option1: "Google",
        option2: "Apple",
        option3: "Microsoft",
        option4: "Facebook",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What is Dart primarily used for?",
        option1: "Web development",
        option2: "Mobile app development",
        option3: "Game development",
        option4: "Data analysis",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the entry point for a Dart application?",
        option1: "main.dart",
        option2: "index.html",
        option3: "app.js",
        option4: "start.php",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Which IDE is commonly used for Dart development?",
        option1: "Visual Studio Code",
        option2: "Eclipse",
        option3: "Sublime Text",
        option4: "Atom",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What does Dart use for asynchronous programming?",
        option1: "Promises",
        option2: "Callbacks",
        option3: "Futures",
        option4: "Generators",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is not a Dart data type?",
        option1: "int",
        option2: "float",
        option3: "String",
        option4: "bool",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the correct way to declare a variable in Dart?",
        option1: "var x = 10;",
        option2: "x = 10;",
        option3: "int x = 10;",
        option4: "let x = 10;",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of the following code?\n```dart\nvar x = 5;\nprint(++x);\n```",
        option1: "5",
        option2: "6",
        option3: "10",
        option4: "Compiler Error",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the correct way to define a function in Dart?",
        option1: "function myFunction() {}",
        option2: "def myFunction() {}",
        option3: "void myFunction() {}",
        option4: "myFunction() {}",
        ans: 3,
    },
];
